<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>
	<template name="Renewal Hardware" id="renewal-hardware">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h2>
				<strong t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">Hardware CCP</strong>
				<strong t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">CCP pour Instruments</strong>
			</h2>
			<br />
			<h4 t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">WHY RENEW YOUR HARDWARE CCP?</h4>
			<h4 t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">Pourquoi Renouveler vos CCP pour vos Instruments?</h4>

			<div class="red-div" />
			<p t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'" id="hardware">New features and bug fixes to the firmware are constantly being worked on and updates
				are typically available every few months. It's also important to keep your instrument running
				smoothly with servicing and calibration. Some of your customers may even require that you have
				a recent calibration certificate to prove your instrument is functioning properly. Having a CCP
				also gives you access to technical support for the product. Further options allow you to extend
				your warranty (BRONZE, SILVER, and GOLD) and the GOLD CCPs include a free loaner instrument while
				your instrument is down or away on repair/calibration.</p>
			<p t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'" id="hardware">De nouvelles fonctionnalités et corrections de bogues sont constamment mises au point et les mises à
				jour sont généralement disponibles 3-4 fois par année. Il est également important de garder votre instrument en bon état avec l'entretien et
				l'étalonnage. Certains de vos clients exigent même que vous ayez un certificat d'étalonnage récent pour prouver que votre instrument
				fonctionne correctement. Avoir un CCP vous donne également accès à un support technique pour le produit. D'autres options vous permettent
				d'étendre votre garantie (BRONZE, ARGENT et OR) tandis que les CCP OR incluent un instrument en prêt gratuitement pendant que votre
				instrument est en panne ou en réparation/étallonage.</p>
			<p t-out="isPDF" />
			<img t-if="isPDF == False" src="" alt="" id="chart" />
			<img t-elif="isPDF == True" src="" alt="" id="chartPDF" />
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal" id="renewal-software">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h2>
				<strong t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">Software CCP</strong>
				<strong t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">CCP pour Logiciels</strong>
			</h2>
			<h4 t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<h4 t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">Pourquoi Renouveler vos CCP Logiciel?</h4>
			<div class="red-div" />
			<p t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available
				every few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop
				working properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical
				support for the product.
			</p>
			<p t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">
				De nouvelles fonctionnalités et corrections de bogues sont constamment mises au point et des mises à jour de nos logiciels sont
				disponibles plusieurs fois par année. Il est également important de garder tous vos produits à jour ensemble car ils peuvent cesser
				de fonctionner correctement si certains sont renouvelés et d'autres ne le sont pas. Avoir un CCP vous donne également accès à un
				support technique pour le produit.
			</p>
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal Subscription" id="renewal-subscription">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h2>
				<strong t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">Software Subscriptions</strong>
				<strong t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">Abonnements Logiciels</strong>
			</h2>
			<h4 t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'">WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE SUBSCRIPTIONS?</h4>
			<h4 t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">Pourquoi Renouveler vos Abonnements Logiciel?</h4>
			<div class="red-div" />
			<p t-if="clang ==  'en_CA' or clang == 'en_US'"> New features and bug fixes are constantly being released and updates to our software are released several times a year. It is also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop working properly if some are renewed and others are not. A subscription gives you the possibility to be up to date and have access to the software at all times until the expiry of the subscription. If the product is not renewed, you lose access to this software on the expiration date. <br /> In the "Additional subscriptions" section, you can choose to add products and their quantities. In the “Existing subscriptions” section, you can choose whether or not to renew the products you already have. </p>
			<p t-elif="clang == 'fr_CA'">De nouvelles fonctionnalités et corrections de bogues sont constamment mises au point et les mises à jour sont généralement disponibles 3-4 fois par année. Il est également important de garder votre instrument en bon état avec l'entretien et l'étalonnage. Certains de vos clients exigent même que vous ayez un certificat d'étalonnage récent pour prouver que votre instrument fonctionne correctement. Avoir un CCP vous donne également accès à un support technique pour le produit. D'autres options vous permettent d'étendre votre garantie (BRONZE, ARGENT et OR) tandis que les CCP OR incluent un instrument en prêt gratuitement pendant que votre instrument est en panne ou en réparation/étallonage.</p>

		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal English" id="renewal-hardware-english" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal-hardware" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-EN.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">CCP Options Chart</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chartPDF&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-EN.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">CCP Options Chart</attribute>
			<attribute name="style">max-height: 79% !important; width:auto !important;</attribute>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal French" id="renewal-hardware-french" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal-hardware" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-FR.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">Tableau des options CCP</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chartPDF&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-FR.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">Tableau des options CCP</attribute>
			<attribute name="style">max-height: 79% !important; width:auto !important;</attribute>
		</xpath>
	</template>
</odoo>