<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>
	<template name="Rental Terms" id="rental_terms">
		<h1>
			<strong>Terms and Conditions</strong>
		</h1>
		<ol>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>Rental, Effective Date and Term</strong>
				</h3>
				<p>
					The Customer hereby rents Equipment from
					<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
					, for the period indicated in the preamble
					of this Agreement, following the terms and
					conditions established hereinafter. The
					Agreement comes into effect on the date
					it is signed by the Customer and expires
					at the end of the Equipment rental period
					indicated in the preamble of this Agreement.</p>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>Considerations</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Rent and Fees
						</h4>
						<p>
							In consideration of renting the Equipment, the Customer agrees to pay
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							the rent and fees indicated on the first page of this Agreement, in addition to applicable taxes.
							If the Customer remains in possession of the Equipment after the Term, with the consent of
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, this Agreement shall remain in force and the Customer shall be the deemed the renter of the
							Equipment, following the same terms, conditions and commitments as those stipulated in this Agreement
							(including payment of any rent).
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Additional Services or Additional Fees
						</h4>
						<p>
							In the event that the Customer requires any other service from AB Tech that is not included in this
							Agreement or additional fees apply to the amounts indicated in this Agreement, the Customer agrees 
							to pay
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							any such amount or fee following receipt of an invoice to that effect.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Interest
						</h4>
						<p>
							Any amounts owing to AB Tech by the Customer shall bear interest at the rate of twenty-four percent
							(24%) per year, as of the date on which such amounts are due.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
		</ol>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal" id="renewal">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR HARDWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p id="hardware">New features and bug fixes to the firmware are constantly being worked on and updates
		 	are typically available every few months. It's also important to keep your instrument running 
		 	smoothly with servicing and calibration. Some of your customers may even require that you have 
		 	a recent calibration certificate to prove your instrument is functioning properly. Having a CCP
			also gives you access to technical support for the product. Further options allow you to extend
		   	your warranty (BRONZE, SILVER, and GOLD) and the GOLD CCPs include a free loaner instrument while
		    your instrument is down or away on repair/calibration.</p>
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available
			every few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop 
			working properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical
			support for the product.</p>
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available every
			few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop working
			properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical support
			for the product.</p>
			<img src="" alt="" id="chart"/>
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal English" id="renewal-english" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-EN.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">CCP Options Chart</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//p[@id=&quot;hardware&quot;]">
			<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="move"/>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal French" id="renewal-french" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-FR.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">Tableau des options CCP</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//p[@id=&quot;hardware&quot;]">
			<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="move"/>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template id="rental-quote-top">

	</template>

	<template id="rental-quote-bottom"></template>
</odoo>