<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>
	<template name="Rental Terms" id="rental_terms">
		<h1>
			<strong>Terms and Conditions</strong>
		</h1>
		<ol>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>Rental, Effective Date and Term</strong>
				</h3>
				<p>
					The Customer hereby rents Equipment from
					<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
					, for the period indicated in the preamble
					of this Agreement, following the terms and
					conditions established hereinafter. The
					Agreement comes into effect on the date
					it is signed by the Customer and expires
					at the end of the Equipment rental period
					indicated in the preamble of this Agreement.</p>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>Considerations</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Rent and Fees
						</h4>
						<p>
							In consideration of renting the Equipment, the Customer agrees to pay
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							the rent and fees indicated on the first page of this Agreement, in addition to applicable taxes.
							If the Customer remains in possession of the Equipment after the Term, with the consent of
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, this Agreement shall remain in force and the Customer shall be the deemed the renter of the
							Equipment, following the same terms, conditions and commitments as those stipulated in this Agreement
							(including payment of any rent).
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Additional Services or Additional Fees
						</h4>
						<p>
							In the event that the Customer requires any other service from AB Tech that is not included in this
							Agreement or additional fees apply to the amounts indicated in this Agreement, the Customer agrees 
							to pay
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							any such amount or fee following receipt of an invoice to that effect.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Interest
						</h4>
						<p>
							Any amounts owing to AB Tech by the Customer shall bear interest at the rate of twenty-four percent
							(24%) per year, as of the date on which such amounts are due.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>
						<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
						's COMMITMENTS
					</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Equipment Condition
						</h4>
						<p>
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							agrees to provide functional Equipment in proper maintenance to the Customer
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Equipment Delivery
						</h4>
						<p>
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							agrees to deliver the Equipment to the Customer at the agreed upon location.
							The Customer acknowledges having given
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							all relevant information on the Equipment delivery location and that such information
							complies with whatever is indicated in this Agreement, as applicable.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>CUSTOMERS COMMITMENTS</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Equipment Use
						</h4>
						<p>
							The Customer agrees to use the Equipment and its accessories solely for the purposes for which
							such Equipment and accessories are intended. The Customer agrees to comply with any requirements
							and regulations on the use of the Equipment that may be required by
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							from time to time. The Customer must not remove any accessory from the Equipment. The Customer
							must not, at any time, authorize any person other than its employees, representatives or agents to
							use the Equipment.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Returning the Equipment to
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
						</h4>
						<p>
							The Customer agrees to return the Equipment to AB Tech in the same operating and clean condition as at
							the time of delivery, and to the same location as the original point of delivery, or failing that to any
							AB Tech branch.
							In such case, the Customer agrees to wash the Equipment prior to its pickup by
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							. The Customer agrees to immediately notify
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							of any damages caused to the Equipment. In such case, the Customer must reimburse
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							for any repairs required as a result of the damages, alterations or stemming from the
							abusive use of the Equipment, for both aesthetic and technical aspects, whether or not such damage,
							alteration or abusive use was intentional by the Customer. Such repairs must be carried out
							exclusively by
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							or its authorized supplier. Under no circumstances is the Customer authorized
							or would be authorized to carry out any repair or have any repair carried out on the Equipment.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Insurance</h3>
						<p>
							The Customer hereby agrees to hold general liability insurance covering any third-party liability
							incumbent upon it (including renter’s insurance) under the terms of this Agreement, with minimum
							coverage of two million dollars ($2,000,000) and to provide a copy of the policy to
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							should
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							so request it.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Standards, Policies and Others</h3>
						<p>
							The Customer hereby agrees to respect and comply with any standard, policy or regulation issued by
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, particularly in regards to the use and safety of the Equipment.</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>INDEMNIFICATION</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>Non-Liability</h4>
						<p>
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							shall, at no time, be held liable for any damages, breakage, or partial or full interruption
							that could result, at any time, during the use of the Equipment. The Customer is solely responsible
							for the individuals who may be required to use the Equipment, throughout the Term of the Agreement.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Indemnification</h4>
						<p>
							The Customer acknowledges that
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, its directors, officers, employees, agents, volunteers and subcontractors, cannot be held
							liable for any breakage, loss, destruction of property and/or damage, of any kind, resulting
							from the use of the Equipment. The Customer waives any right, recourse, claim and action against
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, its directors, officers, employees, agents, volunteers and subcontractors resulting from the use
							of the Equipment. The Customer agrees to indemnify and hold
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							harmless against any claim, of any type, resulting from or could result from any failure by the
							Customer in respecting its obligations under the terms of this Agreement or for any breakage,
							loss, destruction of property and/or damage, of any type, resulting from the use of the Equipment.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>END OF AGREEMENT</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>Termination as of Right</h4>
						<p>
							This Agreement shall be terminated as of right without any notice or formal demand being required from
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							, if the Customer makes a general assignment of its property for the benefit of its creditors, or if
							it is declared bankrupt or insolvent or if it allows its assets to be seized further to a writ of
							execution or other legal proceedings.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Termination on Notice
						</h4>
						<p>
							The Agreement is terminated upon the expiry of a 10 day limit, as of the delivery of a written notice
							indicating, as applicable, the failure to perform by either party, should the defaulting party not
							correct such failure within that time limit, in either of the following cases (i) the Customer breaches
							or does not comply with any of the terms, clauses, conditions and stipulations of the Agreement, and
							the Customer will be required to pay any amounts owing to
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							or (ii) if
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							breaches or does not comply with any of the terms, clauses, conditions and stipulations of the Agreement.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Effect of Termination
						</h4>
						<p>
							When this Agreement is terminated, the Customer agrees to pay AB Tech any amounts owing under the
							terms of the Agreement.
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							may, at any time and without prior notice as of termination, retake
							possession of the Equipment and the Customer hereby authorizes
							, its agents, employees or
							representatives to enter onto its property or on any location where the Equipment is found for the
							purpose of immediately retaking possession of said Equipment, all at the Customer's expense.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
			<li>
				<h3>
					<strong>GENERAL PROVISIONS</strong>
				</h3>
				<ol>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Assignment
						</h4>
						<p>
							<span t-esc="doc.company_id.name"/>
							reserves the right to assign or transfer a portion of or all its rights and obligations resulting
							from this Agreement to anyone, without the need to request the Customer's consent or approval.
							However, the Customer may not assign its rights nor request or allow a third party to assume its
							obligations under this Agreement.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Notice
						</h4>
						<p>
							Any notice required under this Agreement is adequate if it is recorded in writing and sent by a
							method of communication that allows the sending party to prove that said notice was effectively
							delivered to the receiving party at the addresses indicated on the first page of the Agreement or
							any other address the receiving party may have made known in accordance with this Agreement.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Non-Waiver
						</h4>
						<p>
							If either party should waive, neglect or delay the exercise of a right or recourse provided by
							this Agreement, this shall never be held against said party as a renunciation of its rights and
							recourses, as long as the conventionally or legally prescribed time for exercising said right or
							recourse has not expired.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Legal Representatives
						</h4>
						<p>
							The Agreement binds the parties, their successors, legal representatives, liquidators, trustees and assigns.
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>
							Applicable Laws and Jurisdiction
						</h4>
						<p>
							This Agreement and its interpretation, execution, application, validity and effects are subject to
							the applicable laws in force in the province of Ontario and in force in Canada that apply in the
							province of Ontario, which govern all of the provisions it contains.
							The parties agree that any claim or any legal action taken for any reason with respect to this
							Agreement shall be brought to a court located in the judicial district of Toronto, Ontario, Canada,
							to the exclusion of any other judicial district that may have jurisdiction over such disputes under
							the law.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
		</ol>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal" id="renewal">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR HARDWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p id="hardware">New features and bug fixes to the firmware are constantly being worked on and updates
		 	are typically available every few months. It's also important to keep your instrument running 
		 	smoothly with servicing and calibration. Some of your customers may even require that you have 
		 	a recent calibration certificate to prove your instrument is functioning properly. Having a CCP
			also gives you access to technical support for the product. Further options allow you to extend
		   	your warranty (BRONZE, SILVER, and GOLD) and the GOLD CCPs include a free loaner instrument while
		    your instrument is down or away on repair/calibration.</p>
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available
			every few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop 
			working properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical
			support for the product.</p>
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available every
			few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop working
			properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical support
			for the product.</p>
			<img src="" alt="" id="chart"/>
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal English" id="renewal-english" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-EN.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">CCP Options Chart</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//p[@id=&quot;hardware&quot;]">
			<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="move"/>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal French" id="renewal-french" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-FR.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">Tableau des options CCP</attribute>
		</xpath>
		<xpath expr="//p[@id=&quot;hardware&quot;]">
			<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="move"/>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template id="rental-quote-top">

	</template>

	<template id="rental-quote-bottom"></template>
</odoo>