<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>
	<template name="Renewal Hardware" id="renewal-hardware">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR HARDWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p id="hardware">New features and bug fixes to the firmware are constantly being worked on and updates
		 	are typically available every few months. It's also important to keep your instrument running 
		 	smoothly with servicing and calibration. Some of your customers may even require that you have 
		 	a recent calibration certificate to prove your instrument is functioning properly. Having a CCP
			also gives you access to technical support for the product. Further options allow you to extend
		   	your warranty (BRONZE, SILVER, and GOLD) and the GOLD CCPs include a free loaner instrument while
		    your instrument is down or away on repair/calibration.</p>
			<img src="" alt="" id="chart"/>
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal" id="renewal">
		<div id="renewal-text">
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available
			every few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop 
			working properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical
			support for the product.</p>
			<h4>WHY RENEW YOUR SOFTWARE CCP?</h4>
			<div class="red-div"/>
			<p>New features and bug fixes are constantly being worked on and updates to our software are available every
			few months. It's also important to keep all your products up to date together as they may stop working
			properly if some are renewed and others aren't. Having a CCP also gives you access to technical support
			for the product.</p>
		</div>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal English" id="renewal-english" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal-hardware" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-EN.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">CCP Options Chart</attribute>
		</xpath>
	</template>

	<template name="Renewal French" id="renewal-french" inherit_id="proquotes.renewal-hardware" primary="True">
		<xpath expr="//img[@id=&quot;chart&quot;]" position="attributes">
			<attribute name="src">https://cdn.r-e-a-l.it/images/quote-images/CCP-Graphic-FR.png</attribute>
			<attribute name="alt">Tableau des options CCP</attribute>
		</xpath>
	</template>
</odoo>